jobnol.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - JOBNOL

_This privacy policy sets out how JOBNOL uses and protects any information that you give when you using this website._  
_  
__JOBNOL is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. JOBNOL may change this privacy policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes._  
_This privacy policy is effective from 21-03-2015. and Last Updated on 02/08/2016._  
_**  
**__**What We Collect**_  
_JOBNOL collects the following information:_

  * _We do not collect any information by which a person or the visitor is identifiable through our website cookies._
  * _Sometimes we do collect  some data about yourself (Name, Email, Phone No) in our website through Google Form. We use that information to send you notification/newsletter from our websites with your permission. We do not sell your information._

_**What We Do With The Information We Gather**_  
_JOBNOL requires this information to better understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:_

  * _Although we do not collect any  personally identifiable information, but some small chunks of information may be detected through cookies. _
  * _We may use the information to see our website usage and also to improve our services._
  * _We do use Facebook Pixel, Google Analytics to track our website usage only. (Not who are using it)_

_**Security**_  
_We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online._  
_**  
**__**How We Use Cookies**_  
_A cookie is a small file that asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences._  
_We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system._  
_Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us._  
_You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website._  
_**  
**__**Links to Other Websites**_  
_Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement._  
_You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question._  
_**  
**__**Questions About This Privacy Policy**_  
_If you have any questions about this privacy policy, you can contact us through any of the available methods listed on our Contact page._
